sutton.com 2019-12-11

# Privacy Policy - Sutton — Canadian Real Estate Listings & Agents | Sutton.com

### Privacy Policy

We understand the power that the Internet holds for changing your life and making things easier for you. These benefits are at risk if people are concerned about their personal privacy. We are committed to providing you with an Internet experience that respects and protects your personal privacy choices and concerns.

In general, we gather information about all of our users collectively. We only use such information anonymously and in the aggregate. This information helps us determine what is most beneficial for our users, and how we can continually create a better overall experience for you.

### Email Links

This site provides email address link located on the Contact Us page so that you may email  directly with any questions or comments you may have. This site reads all messages received and makes efforts to respond promptly. In addition to replying to your comment or inquiry, your email may also be filed for future reference regarding improvements to our website or discard the information. Your personal information is not shared, traded, sold, or exchanged with any third parties without your express permission.

### Information Collection and Use

This site and the provider ("Four Walls Digital") is the sole owner of the information collected. We will not sell, share, trade or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. This site collects information from our users at several different points on our website. We ONLY collect personal information necessary to effectively market and to sell the property of sellers, to locate, assess and qualify properties for buyers and to otherwise provide professional services to clients and customers. We do not sell, trade, transfer, rent or exchange your personal information with anyone.

### Personal Information  

This site functionality requires/requests users to give us contact information (such as their email address) and personal information (such as their names, address phone numbers, and property details). The visitors contact and personal information is used to contact visitor when necessary and requested, but is primarily used to collect personal information necessary to effectively market and to sell the property of sellers, to locate, assess and qualify properties for buyers and to otherwise provide professional services to clients and customers. We do not sell, trade, transfer, rent or exchange your personal information with anyone. We do not disclose information about your individual visits to this site, or personal information that you provide, such as your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, etc., to any outside parties, except when we believe the law requires it.

### Legal Disclaimer

We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process serviced on our website.

### Links

This site contains links to other sites. These sites have their own policies and practices with respect to online privacy, and This site cannot be responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these Web sites. In addition, in certain instances a This site advertiser may ask you for personal information. This site cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of its advertisers. 

### Notification of Changes

This policy may be revised over time as new features are added to the website. We will post those changes so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. Please check this site for information about revisions to our privacy policy. We will notify you directly if there is a material change in our privacy practices. We will take commercially reasonable measures to obtain written or active e-mail consent from the user, if this site is going to be using the information collected from the user in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection. We will also post the changes in our privacy statement 10 days prior to a change.
